let questions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 20 x 5 + 20 = ? ',
    answer: '120',
    option: ['120', '500', '125', '130'],
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 6! = ?',
    answer: '720',
    option: ['600', '500', '720', '700'],
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 100 + 200 / 10 = ?',
    answer: '120',
    option: ['100', '120', '130', '90'],
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 3! = ?',
    answer: '6',
    option: ['6', '5', '4', '3'],
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 3! + 4! = ?',
    answer: '30',
    option: ['20', '15', '35', '30'],
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 100 x 100 + 1 = ?',
    answer: '1001',
    option: ['1000', '1002', '1001', '1003'],
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 1 x 0 + 1 = ?',
    answer: '1',
    option: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 20 x 10 + 20 + 1 = ?',
    answer: '221',
    option: ['200', '210', '220', '221'],
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 90 + 10 x 10 ?',
    answer: '190',
    option: ['170', '190', '180', '195'],
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question: 'Nilai dari : 50 / 2 + 25 ?',
    answer: '50',
    option: ['25', '20', '15', '10'],
  },
];
